Guide to the Abe Burrows papers, 1904-1993
The New York Public Library. Billy Rose Theatre Division.
- Series II: General Correspondence, 1939-1982; 588315; 15 boxes
  - Sub-series 1 - Letters, 1939-1982; 588316; 12 boxes
    - Correpondence / David Karr,., 1964-1965; 588474; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence / Lawrence Kasha,., 1962-1967; 588475; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / Madeleine Kasket,., 1963-1975; 588476 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence / George S. (George Simon) Kaufman, 1952-1955 and n.d; 588477; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence / Sylvia Fine,., 1954-1973; 588478; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence / Elia Kazan, 1955-1957 and n.d; 588479; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
      Correspondence between Molly and Elia Kazan and Abe Burrows.
      Kazan, Molly, 1906-1963
    - Correspondence / Emil Kelemen,., 1960-1972; 588480; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
      Letters and brochures to Abe Burrows from the artist Emil Kelemen.
    - Correspondence / Gene Kelly,., 1954-1958; 588481; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Two notes to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Robert F. Kennedy,., 1965; 588482; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence / Jean Kerr, 1966-1976 and n.d; 588483; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence / Michael Kidd,., 1955-1970; 588484; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence / Sidney Kingsley, 1954-1968 and n.d; 588485; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence / Harry Kurnitz,., 1946-1968; 588486; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 19)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Also a memorial tribute to Harry Kurnitz.
    - General correspondence, "Ka",., 1951-1979; 588487; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - General correspondence, "Ke",., 1950-1980; 588488; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - General correspondence, "Ki-Kl",., 1952-1981; 588489; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - General correspondence, "Kn-Ko",., 1951-1981; 588490; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - General correspondence, "Kr-Ku",., 1950-1975; 588491; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence / Guy Jourdan de la Passardiere, 1953-1966 and n.d; 588492; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows and typescript speech by La Passardiere entitled The Remarkability of Women!!!
    - Correspondence / Fernando Lamas,., 1956; 588493; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 26)
      Letters [3 p.] to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / John Lahr,., 1964-1969; 588494; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence / Lake Tarleton Club (Pike, N. H.),., 1952-1958; 588495; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence / Abe Lastfogel,., 1948-1968; 588496; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence / Charles Laughton,., 1951; 588497; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 30)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows consists of a draft of Burrows' letter of congratulations and Laughton's thanks.
    - Correspondence / Jerome Lawrence,., 1961-1966; 588498; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 31)
      Two thank you notes for opening night wires to Abe Burrows from Lawrence and Lee.
      Lee, Robert Edwin, 1918-
    - Correspondence / Steve Lawrence,., 1965; 588499; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 32)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows and one photograph of Lawrence.
    - Correspondence / Martin Leeds,., 1968-1969; 588500; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence / Menyhert Lengyel,., 1956-1957; 588501; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Correspondence between Melchior Lengyel and Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Sam Levene, 1953-1957 and n.d; 588502; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows and one letter, 1981, from Levene's son, Joe.
    - Correspondence / Arthur Lewis,., 1952-1974; 588503; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence / Sinclair Lewis,., 1946-1947; 588504; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Letters and contract with Abe Burrows on the dramatization of Lewis' Babbitt.
      Lewis, Sinclair, 1885-1951; Babbitt
    - Correspondence / Franz Lidz,., 1976-1977; 588505; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Lidz introduces himself as a cousin of Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Goddard Lieberson, 1953-1977 and n.d; 588506; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Four letters to Abe Burrows from Goddard and Brigitta Lieberson.
    - Correspondence / Howard Lindsay,., 1951-1969; 588507; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Correspondence between Howard Lindsay, Russel Crouse and Abe Burrows.
      Crouse, Russel, 1893-1966
    - Correspondence / Gerald M. Loeb,., 1964-1965; 588508; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence / Frank Loesser,., 1944-1976; 588509; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Also correspondence and memorial writings about Loesser and business correspondence about royalties, etc.
      Loesser, Lynn
    - Correspondence / Lynn Loesser,., 1952-1975; 588510; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence / Joshua Logan,., 1953-1969; 588511; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence / Anita Loos,., 1967-1970; 588512; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence / Allen Ludden,., 1962; 588513; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 14)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows about Mark Goodson and Bill Todman.
      Goodson, Mark; Todman, William S., 1918-1979
    - Correspondence / Louis R. Lurie,., 1958-1969; 588514; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence / Leonard Lyons,., 1944-1977; 588515 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - General correspondence, "La",., 1948-1979; 588516; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - General correspondence, "Lea-Let",., 1950-1981; 588517; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - General correspondence, "Lev-Lew",., 1950-1980; 588518; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - General correspondence, "Li",., 1953-1980; 588519; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - General correspondence, "Ll-Ly",., 1951-1977; 588520; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence / Nila Mack, 588521; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 22)
      Two letters to Abe Burrows about his Guys and Dolls.
    - Correspondence / Philip Malicoat,., 1955-1971; 588522; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 23)
      Correspondence between Philip and Barbara Malicoat and Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Fredric March,., 1961 Nov 13; 588523; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 24)
      One thank you letter to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Judd Marmor,., 1949-1976; 588524; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence / Arnold Marquis,., 1956-1960; 588525; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence / Joe Marr,., 1948-1970; 588526; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 27)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Also one photograph.
    - Correspondence / Armina Marshall,., 1963; 588527; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence / Ernest H. Martin,., 1953-1965; 588528; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence / Groucho Marx,., 1950-1951; 588529; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 30)
      Two letters [3 p.] to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Walter Matthau,., 1964-1968; 588530; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence / Fred McCarthy,., 1963-1964; 588531; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows and cartoon drawings by McCarthy.
    - Correspondence / Ken McCormick,., 1948-1981; 588532; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Correspondence between Abe Burrows and Ken McCormick, editor-in-chief at Doubleday & Co.
    - Correspondence / Alec McCowen, 1976 and n.d; 588533; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence / J. A. McFadden,., 1951-1963; 588534; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence / St. Clair McKelway,., 1969; 588535; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
      Letter sent to Abe Burrows discusses an idea for a Broadway musical, with New Yorker article by McKelway on which a movie on same theme, Mr. Eighty Eighty, 1950, was based.
    - Correspondence / Shepherd Mead,., 1962-1978; 588536; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence / Doro Merande, 1950-1956 and n.d; 588537; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence / Jo Mielziner, 1953-1954 and n.d; 588538; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / Ed Mitchell,., 1949-1977; 588539; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Includes the We Love Abe Burrows Club of Northern California.
      We Love Abe Burrows Club of Northern California
    - Correspondence / Elick Moll,., 1959-1960; 588540; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence / Ferenc Molnar,., 1951 Apr 17; 588541; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Handmade card to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Mary Tyler Moore,., 1977; 588542; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence / Agnes Moorehead, 1963 and n.d; 588543; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence / Henry Morgenthau,., 1951-1963; 588544; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Correspondence with to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Stanwood Morrill,., 1948; 588545; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows concerns the sponsorship by Lambert Pharmacal Company of St. Louis, Missouri of his radio show on CBS.
    - Correspondence / Robert Morse,., 1963-1973; 588546; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - General correspondence, "Mac-Man",., 1945-1980; 588547; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - General correspondence, "Mar-Mas",., 1945-1980; 588548; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - General correspondence, "Mat-Mc",., 1951-1980; 588549; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - General correspondence, "Me",., 1953-1976; 588550; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - General correspondence, "Mi",., 1948-1970; 588551; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - General correspondence, "Mo",., 1951-1981; 588552; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - General correspondence, "Mu",., 1952-1969; 588553; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence / Ogden Nash, 588554; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 24)
      One letter to Abe Burrows requesting Guys and Dolls tickets.
    - Correspondence / Victor S. Navasky,., 1976; 588555; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence / Barry Nelson,., 1977 Nov 10; 588556; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence / New Dramatists Committee, Inc,., 1957-1977; 588557; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 27)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Also includes some reports, press releases, programs, pamphlets, form letters and address lists of the staff.
    - Correspondence / New Utrecht High School,., 1950-1974; 588558; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 28)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows, primarily with the school's alumni association.
    - Correspondence / New Yorker Magazine, Inc,., 1951-1962; 588559; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence / Mike Nichols,., 1964-1968; 588560; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Four letters to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Robert Nichols,., 1966-1970; 588561; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Four letters and one card to Abe Burrows.
    - General correspondence, "Na-Nev",., 1951-1980; 588562; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, "New-Nu",., 1950-1981; 588563; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence / Edwin O'Connor,., 1963-1967; 588564; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Two letters to Abe Burrows and writings, 1969, about the writer, Edwin O'Connor, after his death.
      O'Connor, Edwin; Correspondence
    - Correspondence / John O'Hara,., 1956-1961; 588565; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence / Laurence Olivier,., 1960 Oct 6; 588566; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence / Maureen O'Sullivan, 588567; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - General correspondence, "O",., 1950-1980; 588568; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence / William Pahlman,., 1953-1980; 588569; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 10)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Includes statements of account and publicity brochures for Pahlman's interior design firm.
    - Correspondence / Norman Panama, 1968-1980 and n.d; 588570; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence / George Panetta,., 1958-1960; 588571; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence / Estelle Parsons,., 1956-1957; 588572; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 13)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Also two photographs.
    - Correspondence / Ted Patrick,., 1947-1953; 588573; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 14)
      Correspondence between Abe Burrows and Ted Patrick, editor of Holiday.
    - Correspondence / Gregory Peck,., 1977 Apr 26; 588574; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence / Norman Perlman,., 1950-1956; 588575; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 16)
      Correspondence between Norman and Polly Perlman and Abe and Carin Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Fred Pernitz,., 1955-1960; 588576; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence / Playwriting Institute of America,., 1970-1971; 588577; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 18)
      Letters and proposed outline of the institute sent to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Cole Porter,., 1952-1964,1952; 588578; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 19)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Also includes lyrics for a song and a signed contract.
    - Correspondence / Robert Porterfield,., 1951-1971; 588579; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 20)
      Correspondence between Abe Burrows and Robert Porterfield of the Barter Theatre, the state theater of Virginia in Abingdon, Virginia. Also one deed of property, 1962, between Porterfield and Burrows.
      Barter Theatre
    - Correspondence / Stanley Prager, 1947-1949 and n.d; 588580; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence / Harold Prince,., 1962-1965; 588581; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - General correspondence, "Pa",., 1946-1979; 588582; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 23)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows. Includes correspondence with Edward Padula.
      Padula, Edward, 1916-
    - General correspondence, "Pe",., 1948-1976; 588583; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 24)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows. Includes correspondence with Sam Perrin.
      Perrin, Sam
    - General correspondence, "Ph-Pl",., 1952-1980; 588584; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - General correspondence, "Po-Pu",., 1947-1981; 588585; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence / Anthony Quinn,., 1960 Nov 1; 588586; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 1)
      One letter to Abe Burrows thanking him for an openinig night wire.
    - Correspondence / Don Quinn,., 1962 Apr; 588587; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence / Samson Raphaelson,., 1962-1967; 588588; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence / Janet Mackenzie Rioch,., 1955-1965; 588589; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence / Jerome Robbins,., 1954-1962; 588590; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence / Jack Roche,., 1960-1969; 588591; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence / Richard Rodgers,., 1953-1970; 588592; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence / Billy Rose,., 1949-1963; 588593; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / Sam Rosenberg,., 1957-1980; 588594; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence / Harold Wallace Ross,., 1950-1951; 588595; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence / Harry Ruby,., 1947-1962; 588596; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence / Rosalind Russell,., 1953-1965; 588597; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - General correspondence, "Ra-Re",., 1947-1982; 588598; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - General correspondence, "Rh-Roc",., 1947-1979; 588599; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows. Includes thank you note for opening night wire from Cyril Ritchard.
      Ritchard, Cyril, 1897-1977
    - General correspondence, "Rod-Rose",., 1949-1978; 588600; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - General correspondence, "Rosn-Ry",., 1947-1980; 588601; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence / Dore Schary,., 1959-1964; 588602; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence / Arthur Meier Schlesinger,., 1961-1980; 588603; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence / Arthur Schwartz,., 1961-1969; 588604; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence / Dinah Shore,., 1965; 588605; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence / Phil Silvers, 1956 and n.d; 588606; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence / Neil Simon, 1973 and n.d; 588607; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 22)
      Four notes to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Noble Sissle,., 1954-1955; 588608; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 23)
      Three letters to Abe Burrows and one brochure from Sissle, as president of the Negro Actors Guild of America, Inc.
      Negro Actors Guild of America
    - Correspondence / C. Michael Smith, Jr.,., 1954-1965; 588609; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence / John Steinbeck,., 1955-1968; 588610; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence / F. Chase Taylor,., 1939-1948; 588611; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence / Rex Stout,., 1961-1965; 588612; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence / Jule Styne,., 1951-1968; 588613; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence / Margaret Sullavan, 588614; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence / David Susskind,., 1959-1969; 588615; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence / Gloria Swanson,., 1951-1952; 588616; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence / Herbert Bayard Swope,., 1948-1958; 588617; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 32)
      Six letters to Abe Burrows.
    - General correspondence, "Sa",., 1952-1981; 588618; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 33)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows. Includes correspondence with Leah Salisbury.
      Salisbury, Leah, 1893-1975
    - General correspondence, "Sc",., 1952-1981; 588619; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 34)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows. Includes correspondence with Lars R. Schmidt who produced some of Burrows' musicals in Paris and Sweden.
      Schmidt, Lars R
    - General correspondence, "Se",., 1952-1976; 588620; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 35)
      Correspondence, both personal and professional, of Abe Burrows. Includes correspondence with Gilbert Seldes.
      Seldes, Gilbert, 1893-1970
    - General correspondence, "Sh",., 1948-1979; 588621; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - General correspondence, "Si-Sl",., 1948-1980; 588622; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - General correspondence, "Sm-Sp",., 1949-1979; 588623; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - General correspondence, "St-Sto",., 1947-1976; 588624; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - General correspondence, "Str-Sy",., 1948-1981; 588625; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence / Howard Teichmann,., 1949-1963; 588626; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence / Clara Thompson,., 1952-1959; 588627; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Includes an issue, 1959 Mar, of the newsletter of the William Alanson White Institute that was dedicated to memorializing Thompson, the Institute's director.
    - Correspondence / Michael Todd,., 1957; 588628; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 8)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows and ephemera about Todd's movie, Around the World in 80 days.
      Around the world in 80 days (Motion picture)
    - Correspondence / Leo Townsend,., 1955-1968; 588629; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence / Shepard Traube,., 1955-1972; 588630; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - General correspondence, "T",., 1948-1980; 588631; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - General correspondence, "U",., 1947-1973; 588632; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence / Rudy Vallee,., 1941-1980; 588633; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence / Bobby Van,., 1966-1980; 588634; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows and two photographs of Van.
    - General correspondence, "V",., 1950-1973; 588635; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence / Mrs. Morton Blaine Walker,., 1954-1959; 588636; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Correspondence with Abe Burrows. Almost entirely letters by Walker who tried very persisently but unsuccessfully to get Burrows to produce her unpublished manuscript on Broadway.
    - Correspondence / William S. Warford,., 1953-1967; 588637; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence / Jerome Weidman,., 1959-1966; 588638; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence / L. Arnold Weissberger,., 1951-1974; 588639; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - White House (Washington, D.C.) correspondence,., 1964-1978; 588640; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence / Whitney Museum of American Art,., 1961; 588641; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Letters and other papers to Abe Burrows concern a requested loan he made for a show at the Whitney, "The Theatre Collects American Art".
    - Correspondence with various Who's Who,., 1953-1981; 588642; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence / Edwin Wilson,., 1962-1975; 588643; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence / Adele Wolman,., 1957-1964; 588644; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 9)
      Correspondence between Adele and Sam Wolman and Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Audrey Wood,., 1961-1966; 588645; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence / Herman Wouk,., 1957-1980; 588646; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence / Gretchen Wyler,., 1955-1981; 588647; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - General correspondence, "Wa",., 1950-1968; 588648; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - General correspondence, "We",., 1946-1980; 588649; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - General correspondence, "Wh",., 1952-1978; 588650; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - General correspondence, "Wi",., 1949-1979; 588651; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - General correspondence, "Wn-Wy",., 1949-1973; 588652; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence / Henny Youngman,., 1953-1955; 588653; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - General correspondence, "Y",., 1955-1975; 588654; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence / John Zacherle,., 1961; 588655; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence / Marc Alan Zagoren,., 1964-1967; 588656; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence / Franco Zeffirelli, 1969 and n.d; 588657; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 22)
      Letter and card to Abe Burrows.
    - Correspondence / Maurice Zolotow,., 1954-1980; 588658; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 23)
      Correspondence between Maurice and Charlote Zolotow and Abe Burrows.
      Zolotow, Charlotte, 1915-
    - Correspondence / Albert Zuckerman,., 1963-1971; 588659; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - General correspondence, "Z",., 1960-1974; 588660; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Sub-series 2 - Telegrams, 1947-1981; 588661; 3 boxes
    This sub-series consists of opening night telegrams sent to Burrows, grouped by production and arranged chronologically, 1950-1976, opening night telegrams sent to Burrows for radio broadcasts and night club acts, 1947-1948, miscellaneous non-opening night telegrams sent to Burrows, 1948-1981, telegrams sent by Burrows to cast members of his own shows, opening night telegrams he sent to colleagues in other shows (arranged by date), followed by other non-show related telegrams he sent, 1950-1968. The non-opening night telegrams Burrows received that were found interfiled in the letters sub-series were left where they were found.
    - Guys and Dolls opening night telegrams,., 1950 Oct 12-14; 588662; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 26)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the show opening at the Shubert Theatre in Philadelphia.
      Loesser, Frank, 1910-1969
    - Guys and Dolls opening night telegrams,., 1950 Nov 24; 588663; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 27)
      Telegrams to Abe Burrows on the Broadway opening at the 46th Street Theatre.